

acjh13.github.io



acjh13@gmail.com



Highly adaptive and multi-disciplinary Producer / Project Manager with a technical and design background. Experienced in leading interdisciplinary teams in fast-paced environments. Keen eye for quality and risk assessment. Passionate about elevating teams to excellence by ensuring smooth processes and pipelines.

Industry Experience

Junior Producer | Lionfish Studios Pte Ltd - Various Projects Mar 2021 - Present

- Communicate with and manage project stakeholders and clients
- Assist in overseeing project milestones and releases
- Coordinate project development with multiple cross-functional teams

Production Intern | gumi Asia Pte Ltd - Final Fantasy Brave Exvius Sept 2020 - Feb 2021

- Maintained event lists for content updates with Google Sheets and Confluence
- Responsible for Design team's Sprint Planning and follow up with Jira
- Assisted Associate Producer in integrating new ticketing workflow
- Took initiative to streamline and automate various production workflows
- Involved in documentation of notes for marketing promotional videos

On-Campus Experience

Teaching Assistant | DigiPen Singapore – Game Production Class Sept 2019 - Mar 2020

Advised ~10 student teams on project management and game production

Academic Game Projects

Producer, Editor Programmer, Cinematics Designer

Kindred | Sept 2019 – June 2020, 35 Weeks | 11 Person Team

- 3D narrative game developed on a custom C++ engine and editor with C# scripting
- Led a team with members of various disciplines (Engineering, Design, Art)
- Communicated game's direction across team members and lecturers
- Adopted Agile methodology with weekly Scrum meetings and Kanban task boards
- Created <u>cross-department workflows</u> for better communication
- Finalist in multiple categories, DigiPen Game Awards 2020

Producer, Engine & Editor Programmer

Mega Macho Brothers | Sept 2018 – Apr 2019, 30 Weeks | 7 Person Team

- 2D co-op action platformer developed on a custom C++ engine and editor
- Led a team with members of various disciplines (Engineering, Design, Art)
- Worked with lecturers and team members to resolve internal conflicts
- Awarded Unity Best Sophomore Game, DigiPen Game Awards 2019

For more details on my projects, see my Portfolio!

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Game Design

DigiPen Institute of Technology, Singapore Sept 2017 - Apr 2021 (Expected)

- Dean's Honour List, Fall '19
- Exchange Student DigiPen Redmond, Summer '19

Skills

Soft Skills

Effective Communication Problem Solving Conflict Resolution Project Ownership Team Management

Management Methods

Agile Scrum Kanban

Management Software

Jira / Trello Confluence Google / Microsoft Suite Slack / Discord HacknPlan

Software & Tools

Git / SVN Microsoft Office Visual Studio Unity Unreal Engine 4 Custom Game Engine(s)

Programming Languages

C / C++ C# Python JavaScript

Spoken Languages

English (Native) Mandarin (Limited)